A sound soul, dwells within a sound mind, and a sound body.
Anna!
His wavelength is distorted. It's full of bloodlust.
Now that I'm good and fired up, there'll be no stopping us!
My soul's wavelength holds 800 years of anger and hatred!
Ah!
Now, Ragnarok.
Here we go, Maka.
Right.
I'm so glad you're here!
Let's go!
Love be with you friends with your activation
I don't recognize yours
Thank you.
胸を刺すなら言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
やっと理由を途絶びに突きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
胸を刺すなら言葉よりもっと強い響きが出てくる
心洋を刺すち的な存在 incidentに...
グリゾッドした事立ちの間にある
ヒリザフィルシə Merry Christmas
What caused this incident in Luv Village?
There's only one thing that I can think of.
The soul of the heretic witch could be hiding inside that old golem.
In which case, it could definitely react to the madness wavelengths.
800 years of bloodlust.
Advent of the heretic witch?
Are you ready, Maka?
Yes.
Ragnarok?
Yep.
Go, Dark Sword.
Screech Alpha!
Now!
Too hard.
It may be an old golem, but you're gonna need more than that to bring it down.
I've taken good care of it.
Don't push your luck.
Back away.
It's okay.
I can keep going.
I've managed to get this close with Krona's help.
I'm not going anywhere.
Maka, what's happening?
My...
My body.
Time to chop you into pieces.
What's happening?
Maka!
What's going on?
I can't move.
It's like I'm frozen.
What?
Damn it.
What now?
Crap.
Great.
What do I do?
What's this?
It's thread.
Here it is.
There were mass hallucinations in countries surrounding the Czech Republic.
Nearly 500,000 people reportedly saw mysterious black ball-like things both indoors and outdoors in the area.
No one ever figured out what they were.
With no other explanation available, the case was ultimately considered a mass hallucination.
People who reported hallucinations of the mysterious black objects described them as spider-like.
Spiders.
And the area where most of the hallucinations were reported was...
It was Luth Village.
That settles it.
This wasn't a hallucination.
Eight hundred years ago, when that heretic disappeared, she must have split up her body into the black objects those people saw.
And when that was done, she left her soul inside the old Gola.
What was that?
A spider?
So the spiders scattered across the world have finally gathered.
I've waited for this.
Lord Death, it's Stein.
We need to talk.
Hey there, how ya, how ya doing?
Thanks for coming.
Good to see ya.
Well, what's up?
Have you got something figured out?
Yes.
I believe the heretic witch Arachne scattered her body and left her soul inside the golem that's gone crazy in Luth Village.
Arachne?
That's right.
It makes sense for her to be the first one we've seen dramatically affected by the madness wavelengths.
Even here, I can feel it.
The madness inside me.
Her madness is clawing its way inside my body.
I know it's hard, but try to endure it.
This is too much for Maka and the others to handle alone.
I'll head there now to help them.
Now, now, Stein.
Don't be hasty.
I had a bad feeling about this situation, too, you see.
Necessary measures have already been taken.
Look, the spiders are climbing up it.
They're being drawn into it by the soul I sensed in the golem.
Rona?
Don't worry, I'll protect you, Maka.
The Kishin has been revived.
Its madness runs throughout the world.
While you were sleeping, the Earth suddenly became a fantastic place to live.
Right?
Arachne.
I wonder, is one coffin going to be enough for this job?
Arachne. The mother of magic weapons. This must have happened because of the madness wavelengths. They've stirred her at last from her slumber.
Who knew she was still alive after all this time? The mother of magic weapons, she was responsible for bringing these creations into the world.
She used witches' souls to give them their ability to transform from people into weapons.
She would kill other witches and sacrifice their souls in order to make her terrible weapons.
As a result, she found herself being chased not only by me, but by her fellow witches as well.
Where did you go?
This woman. This Wavelink. Lady Medusa.
It's nice to meet you, children. I've been looking forward to this. Maka. Sol.
Last night you had a little argument, didn't you? Over who it was that burned the curry.
How could you possibly know that? It was Sol. He forgot to turn the burner off and scorched your dinner.
The two of you aren't my only entertainment, though. I've been watching everything that's gone on throughout the world.
For eight centuries. Through the eyes of my dear spiders.
You too, Crona. The child of Medusa. My little sister.
How delightful. Medusa didn't love you one little bit, did she?
Well, it's not too late. I can give you my love.
Who I love.
Oh, how delightful.
Go after a Crona! Kill the witch!
We're on fire now!
A close call. But I guess I have aged a bit in these last 800 years.
I'm no longer delighted. Exterminate the brat, Gerrico.
Shirofe!
No way! He broke through the black blood with just one kick?
My trusty saw leg. Looks like speed setting two is enough to take care of this brat.
I guess Medusa's research was nothing special after all.
Cuts like that are nothing! I'll just harden the black blood after you say thank you!
Thank you!
You mean thanks very much!
They're stronger than I thought.
I guess I'll just have to cut them in half and eat their souls!
Stop it! When you squat, it looks like you're going to the bathroom!
Now we're talking!
Say goodbye, brats!
Time to die!
Nice try!
Saint Cross knife!
Who the hell are you?
His arms are guillotine?
So who won?
Damn, that was close.
That guy almost got me.
It's a good thing I had my chains ready or else I'd be dead by now.
Quite impressive. Who are you anyway?
Too good to answer me, are you?
Justin Law.
He's one of the death scythes.
This guy is a death scythe? You're kidding me.
Is he?
The executioner. He's a legend at the Academy.
Four years ago when he was only 13, he became the youngest boy ever in Academy history to reach the level of death scythe. He did it all by himself too. With no meister partner or anything.
Oh Lord Death, please grant me strength.
Attention DWMA students. As there is only one opponent, I will end this quickly. Please wait a moment if you don't mind.
Damn, he's loud.
Because of the earphones maybe?
Another weapon like me who doesn't need a meister?
Another weapon like me who doesn't need a meister? I don't like that very much.
I don't like that very much.
Oh Lord Death, please grant me strength.
Attention DWMA students. As there is only one opponent, I will end this quickly. Please wait a moment if you don't mind.
Damn, he's loud.
Because of the earphones maybe?
Another weapon like me who doesn't need a meister? I don't like that very much.
Do you have fun sucking up to death, boy? Is it worth it?
They've both got such strong wavelengths. They might be equals.
What is it?
A sight. He's the same kind of weapon I am.
You wanna know something that really pisses me off?
Bootlicking suckers like you!
You're nothing but a vulnerable that Death is housebroken!
Reverse rotation!
Don't you even want to hear about the heretic witch?
Next shackle guard!
Headbutt of love!
You dirty bastard!
They're on such a different level than us. I can't learn anything from this.
What are you trying to study right now? Damn, you're a strange girl!
Now I've got my engine running.
Why don't you take off the damn earphones already?
You're not listening to a single word I'm saying, you cocky bastard!
I can read your lips. I don't have to hear you. Such a filthy mouth. Quite shocking.
You've been reading my lips this whole time? So you purposefully pretended that you couldn't hear me? Now you're really pissing me off!
Giripo.
What do you want, lady?
I detest children who shout. Shouldn't you know that by now?
How can I help you, ma'am?
The Golem's energy is just about drained. It's time for us to begin our retreat.
Retreat?
Someone is waiting for us. But don't worry. You'll have plenty of opportunities to fight later.
There's no choice then. The rest is up to you, Golem. I couldn't care less about those brats.
They'll die soon enough.
Hold it! There's no escaping!
Rona!
Maka!
Lord Death's express instructions were to secure the academy students and the trial student who's with them.
Everyone, please duck down. I'm going to take care of this.
O great lord of ours who dwells within the city of Death, may thy name be kept true.
The prayer is increasing the strength of his soul, Waveling.
O Lord of Death, I am your servant of peace.
I am a pillar of justice.
I am a blade of faith.
In the name of the Great Lord Death, Law-abiding Son of God!
Now then, let us all bow our heads in prayer.
What?
Amazing.
He's the same kind of weapon I am.
And he did all that by himself.
With my Meister immobilized like this, I can't even fight.
All I can do is sit here and hold her.
Dammit.
You still can't move at all, Maka?
Man, that's one stubborn spell Arachne put on you. Doesn't look like it's going anywhere.
I feel so inept.
Uh-huh.
Hey, hold on a sec. Is it really necessary to put me in here?
What?
Come on, I know at least one of you can read my lips.
For now, I guess our best bet is to ask Professor Stein if he can fix her up somehow.
Yes, I agree.
If anyone knows what to do, it'll be him.
Stein's a doctor, after all.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm sure Stein won't do anything weird to me.
Hey, Maka, a flower.
Thank you, Krona.
I think I understand how Sid felt now.
A red carpet here in the middle of the mountains?
I've been awaiting your arrival, Lady Arachne.
Mosquito.
The air here has become quite dry and stagnant in the last 800 years.
It's making me very thirsty.
I have an excellent bottle of champagne chilled and waiting for you.
This car's so cramped and stuffy.
There. That's better.
Huh. You vulgar hoodlum. Show some gratitude.
What? You want a piece of me, old man?
Never mind your squabbling, boys.
I'm exhausted.
Hurry to the castle.
Not only has the Kishan revived, but its madness has also revived the heretic witch Arachne.
Yet another dangerous enemy that must be dealt with.
It's been such a long time.
Lady Arachne, this is the network you have spent 800 years creating.
Congratulations.
Lady Arachne, congratulations on your revival!
I will defeat you. Death.
I will defeat you death
and deny me
iate my end
It's even worse
I will end even by the murders
We must win the ever once
We are here
I can always hear you
We can love the same
I will defeat you
put the surprise
In thecasuelle
ời
You want to see left
So you know, let's see
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
Ahhhh!
Justin, what kind of organization is arachnophobia?
Um, Justin?
Hold on, can't you read lips?
Hey! Justin!
Whatever.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, the sword god rises.
Does it have a sweet or salty taste?
Breast? How dare you speak that way?
I don't think you can read my lips very well.